losapos.com 2011-01-19

# Privacy Policy | www.losapos.com

Your privacy is important to LosApos.com. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. When you create a LosApos.com ID, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and credit card information.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**  
LosApos.com’s website may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

LosApos.com and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with LosApos.com more convenient and personal. 

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. LosApos.com may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**  
Personal information will stay with LosApos.com to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

**Service Providers**  
LosApos.com shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever LosApos.com operates. 

**Others**  
It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for LosApos.com to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

**Protection of Personal Information**  
LosApos.com takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

When you post on LosApos.com, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

LosApos.com makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at LosApos.com. For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if LosApos.com is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made to [info@losapos.com](mailto:info@losapos.com).

**Children**  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible

**Third-Party Sites and Services**  
LosApos.com may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

**Privacy Questions**  
If you have questions or concerns about LosApos.com’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at [info@losapos.com](mailto:info@losapos.com). 

LosApos.com may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

LosApos.com, Villershof 17, 3071 Erps-Kwerps, Belgium

Last updated: August 17, 2010
